You look really nice in these clothes.
（真壁）その服　すごく似合ってるぜ
とてもセクシーだ
Very sexy.
（梨穂子）真壁君…
Makabe-kun?
今日の桜井を見ていたら
俺の中のパッションが
When I look at the you right now, it's like the passion
inside me's about to burst forth or has been awakened...
弾けちゃったっていうか
目覚めたっていうか
なぜ　今まで
気づかなかったか分からないぜ
I don't know why I never noticed it until now.
桜井　お前にホレた
俺と付き合わないか？
Sakurai, I'm in love with you.
Will you go out with me?
でも…　突然　言われても
But... this is all too sudden...
バカだな　恋は
いつも突然始まるものだろう
Don't be silly.
Love is something that always starts suddenly.
「イエス」って言えよ
なッ　いいだろ？
Just say yes.
Well? Why not?
Um... I...
あの…　私
私…　好きな人がいるの
I... have someone I like.
誰だよ！？　それ
私…
Who's he?
I...
私！
I...!
あ～あ　この　俺を振るなんて
後悔しても知らねえからな
Just don't regret having rejected me!
ほッ…
《（香苗）いい加減に
桜井の気持ち》
It's about time you let Tachibana-kun know how you feel.
《橘君に分かって
もらわないとね》
Hey there, girl.
ねえねえ　彼女
俺と付き合わない？
Wanna go out with me?
（はるか）うん？
ああ…
だって　響ちゃん
Says he, Hibiki-chan.
（響）それ　ナンパのつもり？
Are you hitting on her?
し…　失礼しました！
E-Excuse me!
出会った瞬間
Deatta shunkan
From the moment we met
Final8 presents
SS
plus
＋
Amagami
Final8 presents
SS
plus
＋
Amagami
Final8 presents
SS
plus
＋
Amagami
Final8 presents
SS
plus
＋
Amagami
Final8 presents
SS
plus
＋
Amagami
感じてた運命を 確信に変えたくて
Kanjiteta unmei wo kakushin ni kaetakute
I wanted to change this destiny I felt into conviction
Final8 presents
SS
plus
＋
Amagami
Final8 presents
SS
plus
＋
Amagami
Final8 presents
SS
plus
＋
Amagami
Final8 presents
SS
plus
＋
Amagami
Final8 presents
SS
plus
＋
Amagami
Final8 presents
SS
plus
＋
Amagami
Final8 presents
SS
plus
＋
Amagami
Final8 presents
SS
plus
＋
Amagami
Final8 presents
SS
plus
＋
Amagami
Final8 presents
SS
plus
＋
Amagami
Final8 presents
SS
plus
＋
Amagami
Final8 presents
SS
plus
＋
Amagami
Final8 presents
SS
plus
＋
Amagami
Final8 presents
SS
plus
＋
Amagami
Final8 presents
SS
plus
＋
Amagami
Final8 presents
SS
plus
＋
Amagami
SS
plus
＋
Amagami
Final8 presents
SS
plus
＋
Amagami
plus
SS
Final8 presents
Amagami
＋
Final8 presents
Amagami
plus
＋
Amagami
Final8 presents
SS
plus
＋
Amagami
Final8 presents
SS
plus
＋
Amagami
Final8 presents
SS
plus
＋
Amagami
Final8 presents
plus
Amagami
SS
＋
Final8 presents
plus
Amagami
Final8 presents
plus
Amagami
Final8 presents
plus
Amagami
今日も キミのそばにいるのかな
Kyou mo kimi no soba ni iru no ka na
I wonder if I can stay by your side again today
キミのすべてに
Kimi no subete ni
Everything about you
Check My Soul
ハートが動き出した
Haato ga ugokidashita
My heart begins to wake
今 キミと一緒に駆け出そう
Ima kimi to issho ni kakedasou
Let's break into a run together right now
Check My Soul
（チャイム）
≪（美也）は～い
こんばんは
心の声聞いて
Kokoro no koe kiite
Listen to the voice in my heart
≪（美也）梨穂ちゃん　待ってたよ→
ねえねえ　途中で
にぃにに会わなかった？
行こう この胸が高鳴る場所へ
Yukou kono mune ga takanaru basho e
Let's go to a place that will make my heart race
えッ？　ううん　会わなかったよ
夢のような時の中でも
Yume no you na toki no naka de mo
Even in dreamlike moments
おかしいな～
真実だけを見つめていたい
Shinjitsu dake wo mitsumete itai
I only want to gaze at the truth
瞳の奥の
Hitomi no oku no
Inside your eyes
Check My Soul
（純一）ただいま
心の声聞いて
Kokoro no koe kiite
Listen to the voice in my heart
あッ　帰ってきた！
行こう この胸が高鳴る場所へ
Yukou kono mune ga takanaru basho e
Let's go to a place that will make my heart race
Sakurai Rihoko
2nd Half
Wind Chimes
Sakurai Rihoko
2nd Half
Wind Chimes
Sakurai Rihoko
2nd Half
Coming!
Good evening.
Riho-chan! I've been waiting!
Hey, did you see Nii-nii on the way here?
No, I didn't.
Weird.
I'm home!
Ah, he's back.
Aww, the ice cream's all melted!
あ～あ　アイス溶けちゃってる
ああ　ごめん
Sorry.
よ…　よう
H-Hey.
Th-Thanks for having me here.
あッ…　お邪魔してます
What's with you both?
２人とも　どうしたの？
えッ…　いや　別に
It's nothing!
えっと　純一も美也ちゃんも
おなかすいてるよね
U-Um, you must both be hungry.
I'll get the food done quickly, so wait just a little longer.
急いで料理作るから　待ってて
I'll help!
みゃーも手伝う
待て！
Wait!
美也は何もするな
え～　何で！？
Don't you do anything!
Huh? Why?!
Well, you got the dashi and barley tea packs mixed up
the other day and made some funky-tasting miso soup!
だって　この前もダシパックと
麦茶のパックを間違えて
すごい味の味噌汁　作っただろ
Shut up!
うっさ～い！
誰にだって失敗はあるのだ
Everyone makes mistakes.
[ﾃﾚﾋﾞ]用意　ドーン！
ハハハ…　何　このオチ？
What's with that punch line?!
（鼻歌を歌う）
（ドアが開く）
もう少しでできるから　待ってて
I'll be done soon, so just wait a little longer.
うん…　純一？
Junichi?
えっと…
Uh...
I kinda want to ask you something.
ちょっと
聞きたいことがあるというか
何？　聞きたいことって
いや　その…
What is it?
Well, uh...
さっき
買い物に出たときなんだけどさ
When I was out buying some stuff earlier...
さっき？
Earlier?
No, like when I was out buying some stuff earlier.
いや　さっき
買い物に出たときなんだけど
夏休みになると　こうも
カップルが増えるのかなって
I was just thinking you see a lot
more couples come summer break.
梨穂子は　どう思う？
What do you think, Rihoko?
私？　う～ん　そうだな
Me?
Hmm... let's see...
でも　私が
買い物してたときは
I didn't see that many couples when
I was out doing the groceries, though.
あんまりカップルなんて
見かけなかったけどな
Uh, I suppose so!
ああ…　そうだよな
僕が偶然多く
見かけただけだよな
I guess I just happened to see a lot of them.
それだけ？
ああ…
That's all you wanted to ask?
ああ…　それだけかな
Yeah, that's all... I guess.
All right, I'll leave you to it.
じゃあ　また　あとで
純一！
Junichi.
何？
あのね　私…
What?
I... uh...
私　おいしい料理作るから
待ってて
I'll make some really good food, so wait just a little longer.
うん　楽しみに待ってるよ
Yeah, I'm looking forward to it.
（ドアが閉まる）
はあ…　ダメだな　私
I'm so hopeless.
できました～
It's done!
おお～ッ！
Amazing, Riho-chan!
すごいよ　梨穂ちゃん
うまそうだな
It looks really good.
でも　これ
高かったんじゃないのか？
But isn't this pretty expensive stuff?
エヘヘ…　実はね
Actually...
≪（琉璃子）今頃　りほっち
精がつく料理を→
Rihocchi is probably busily making some spirit-inducing food right about now.
それこそ　せっせと
作ってる頃かね
（愛歌）
まさに精魂込めて
With every ounce of her spirit.
また　信じてたね
アハハ…
She fell for it again.
《他にも夏バテ解消料理を
教えよう》
I'll tell you another ingredient that can cure heat fatigue.
《お願いします》
Yes, please do!
《ズバリ　レンコン料理》
Lotus root.
Lotus root is written in Chinese with the characters for "training" and "pole", so it has the meaning of robustness.
《レンコンとは
広東語で練習の「練」》
《棍棒の「棍」と書いて
たくましいという意味があり→》
I hear it's eaten by all swordsmen well-versed in kung fu.
《中国拳法の剣士達が
こぞって食べたといわれる》
《へえ～》
Wow...
Poor girl.
ういヤツ
でも　そろそろ
りほっちの思いが
But it's about time Rihocchi lets Junichi know how she feels.
橘に伝わっても
いい頃じゃない？
Agreed.
同感
あッ！
こ…　これは～！
海の主か！？
C-Could this be...
...the king of the sea?!
≪（琉璃子）おお～ッ！　このッ
逃がすもんか
You're not getting away!
先輩達　大学生活　どうだって？
How are the Senpais' university lives going?
まあまあって言ってたけど
楽しそうだった
They said it was okay, but they seemed to be having fun.
Enbi
Oh yeah, they said they joined the Tennis Circle.
テニスサークルに
入ったって
ええ～ッ　ホントか！？
What? You serious?
ねえ　私も
ビックリしちゃった
I know, right? I was really surprised myself.
う～ん…
《アハハ…》
They still kindly taught me all kinds of things like they used to, though.
でも　相変わらず親切に
色々　教えてくれた
今日のメニューも
先輩から教えてもらったの
In fact, they taught me how to make today's dishes.
I see.
へえ～
むふ～　ごちそうさま
I'm done!
I'm really full.
食った　食った
すごい！
Wow!
Nii-nii's appetite's back!
にぃに　食欲が戻ってきたね
Well, it was really good.
いや～
おいしかったからな
It's a good thing I made the food, then.
そう言ってもらえると
作った甲斐がある
Thanks, Rihoko.
梨穂子　ありがとな
ううん…　純一と美也ちゃんが
そんなに喜んでくれるなら
No problem.
Since it makes you both so happy...
私　また
ご飯作りにきてもいいかな？
Is it okay if I come make dinner again next time?
You're more than welcome to!
大歓迎だよ！　ねッ　にぃに
ああ
Right, Nii-nii?
Yeah.
（電話のベル）
おなかいっぱいで動けないよ
にぃに　出て
I'm so full that I can't move.
Nii-nii, go get it.
I bet it's for you anyway.
どうせ　美也への電話だろ
出てくれよ
You go get it.
ううう…
最初はグー
Rock, paper...
はい　橘です
Hello, Tachibana residence.
Ah, this is Nakata.
（紗江）中多ですけど　美也ちゃん？
あのね　急なんだけど
Miya-chan?
I know it's sudden, but how about going to the amusement park with me if you don't have any other plans tomorrow?
明日　予定がないなら
一緒に遊園地に行かない？
How come?
えッ　何で！？　うん　うん
Ah, right.
ほら　やっぱり
美也への電話じゃないか
See? I knew it'd be for Miya.
梨穂子
うん？
Rihoko.
あの…　片づけ手伝おうか？
Um...
Should I help with the cleaning up?
ありがとう　でも大丈夫だよ
Thanks, but I'll be fine.
純一
うん？
Junichi.
私ね…
え～ッ！
You know, I...
The Inago Masks?!
イナゴマスク！？　面白そう
うん　行く行く　ＯＫ
Sounds really fun!
Yeah, I'll definitely go!
Okay!
逢ちゃんも？　うん
じゃあ　明日　楽しみにしてるね
Ai-chan's going too? Right.
Okay, I'll be looking forward to tomorrow!
明日ね　紗江ちゃんと逢ちゃんとで
遊園地に行くことになったんだ
I'm going to the amusement park
with Sae-chan and Ai-chan tomorrow!
楽しみ　楽しみ～！
Fun, fun!
あッ　そうだ　デザート　デザート
Oh, that's right.
Dessert, dessert!
えッ　さっき
おなかいっぱい…
What? Didn't you say you were full-
デザートは別腹だよ
梨穂ちゃんも食べるよね？
There's a separate stomach for dessert!
Riho-chan, you'll have dessert too, right?
Yeah.
うん
ニシシシ…
美也と梨穂子の別腹には
毎回　驚かされるよ
Your and Miya's "separate stomachs" scare me every time.
ペンギンちゃんの氷かき
Penguin-chan ice shaver~
冷たい冷たい　かき氷
Cold, cold shaved ice~
Penguin-chan ice shaver!
ペンギンちゃんの氷かき
できあがり～！
It's done!
オイ　ちょっと
大盛りすぎないか
Hey, isn't that a little too much?
全部　食べたら　おなか壊すぞ
大丈夫　大丈夫
You'll ruin your stomach if you eat it all.
I'll be fine!
We would've been putting ice cream on instead.
本当は　ここに
アイスがのるはずだったのに
I'm sorry.
反省してます
仕方ないな
Oh well.
ねえ　梨穂ちゃん
美也特製七色かき氷
Hey, Riho-chan.
This is Miya's special seven-colored shaved ice!
Want some?
少し　あげようか？
う…　うん
Right...
That's pretty heavy rain.
すごい　雨だね
うん…
Yeah...
ねえ　梨穂ちゃん
泊まってけば？
Hey, Riho-chan. How about staying the night?
えッ　でも…
Eh? But...
Well, it'll be bad if you catch a cold going home in such heavy rain.
こんな雨の中を帰って
カゼひいたら大変だよ
ねえ　にぃに
その方がいいよね？
Hey, Nii-nii.
It's better this way, right?
えッ…　ああ　そうだな
Yeah, you're right.
梨穂子さえ　よければ
If you don't mind, Rihoko.
ホント？　じゃあ　そうしようかな
Really?
Okay, I'll stay the night.
It's decided, then!
じゃあ　決まり！
〈まさか…〉
I can't believe...
〈純一の家に
泊まることになるなんて〉
I ended up staying over at Junichi's place...
〈何か　今日は一度に
色々なことがありすぎて〉
Way too many things happened today.
I...
〈私…〉
Persistence
Yields Results
〈今度こそ　ちゃんと伝えよう〉
I'll let him know this time, for sure.
はあ～　お風呂気持ちよかったよ～
Ahh, the bath felt really good!
はい　梨穂ちゃんは
このお布団使ってね
Okay, Riho-chan. You'll be using this futon.
ありがとう　美也ちゃん
わざわざ用意してくれて
Thanks for going through the trouble, Miya-chan.
みゃーは　一緒に寝てもいいのに
そうすれば
I wouldn't mind sleeping with you, though.
That way, I could use your soft boobs as a pillow!
そのフカフカな胸を
枕に寝られるもん
ニシシシ…
美也ちゃんったら
Geez, Miya-chan...
ちょっと　いいか？
何？
Can I come in for a bit?
What?
僕の服で　大丈夫だったかなって…
I was just wondering if my clothes are okay...
うん？
フカフカ…
フカフカ？
Soft...
Soft?
へッ！　いや　何でも
No, it's nothing!
で　どう？　僕の服　大丈夫？
So... Well? Are my clothes okay?
Yeah, they fit just right.
うん　ちょうどいいみたい
ありがとう
Thanks.
It's true!
ホントだよ
みゃーの服じゃ
My clothes would've been too tight around here for you to wear.
ここんとこキツくて
着られなかったよ
You did the right thing to borrow Nii-nii's clothes!
にぃにのを借りて　大正解
えッ　そ…　そうだな
Y-Yeah.
Now that you're done, time for you to get out.
さてと　用がすんだら
にぃには出てって
ニシシシ…
（美也の寝息）
うん？
Huh?
ああッ！　美也　違う違う！
Miya! No, no!
う～ん？
寝ぼけてるぞ　美也！
You're still half-asleep, Miya!
あれ？　にぃに
Huh? Nii-nii?
もう　しっかりしろよ
Geez, get a grip on yourself.
トイレ～
Bathroom...
かき氷　食べすぎたんじゃないのか
小学生かよ
I bet it's because you had too much shaved ice.
Are you in elementary school?
（トイレが流れる）
（美也の寝息）
（ドアが閉まる）
うん？
梨穂子か　どうした？
Rihoko, what's wrong?
えッ…　うん　ちょっと眠れなくて
I couldn't fall asleep.
純一こそ　どうしたの？
What about you, Junichi?
Me too.
僕もだよ
何だか目がさえちゃってさ
I feel wide awake for some reason.
雨　やんだね
ああ
The rain stopped.
Yeah.
あの…
花火
Hey-
Fireworks...
花火　やらないか？
Wanna light some fireworks?
うん
Okay.
子供の頃は
夏休みは毎日のように
When we were kids, we'd play with fireworks almost every day during summer break.
花火　やってたよな
うん
Yeah.
Didn't there use to be this firework with a parachute?
昔　パラシュートつきの
花火があっただろ
Yeah, there was.
うん　あったね
純一は花火のあと　空から降りる
小さいパラシュート
You really liked to catch the little parachute that would fall from the sky after it burst.
受け止めるのが好きだったね
梨穂子は昔から
線香花火が好きだったな
You've always liked sparkler fireworks.
うん　何か
Yeah.
It's really cute how the small sparks crackle.
あのパチパチって
小さい火花がカワイイんだもん
Oh yeah, we often used to
compete on whose would last longer.
どっちが長持ちするか
よく競争したよね
《ああッ　チェッ　何だよ》
Oh, come on.
《はい　これ　あげる》
Here, have mine.
《サンキュー》
《あッ！》
Thank you!
《あ～あ》
Aww.
はい　これ
ありがとう
Here, have this.
Thanks.
もうすぐ　高校生活最後の夏休みも
終わっちゃうね～
Our very last high school summer break is ending soon.
Yeah, it sure went by fast.
ああ　早いもんだな
It feels like the school entrance ceremony only just happened.
入学式　つい
この前だった気がするね
うん
Yeah.
ねえ　純一
うん？
Hey, Junichi.
Hmm?
進路は　もう決めた？
Have you decided on what you want to do in the future?
う～ん…　まだかな？
Not yet.
梨穂子の方こそ
決めたのか？
What about you, Rihoko?
Me? I haven't decided yet, either.
私？　私もまだかな～
お互い　そろそろ
決めないとな
Looks like we both need to decide real soon.
うん　そうだね
Yeah, you're right.
幼稚園のときから今日まで
僕達ず～っと一緒だったよな
We've been together the whole time since kindergarten.
Yeah, you're right.
うん　そうだよね
えっと…
Um...
あの…　私
You know, I...
これからも　そうだといいな
It'd be nice if things could stay that way.
えッ！？
えっと　あの…
Um... I...
アチッ！
あッ！　ごめんなさい
Ow!
I'm sorry!
うわッ！
ああッ！
ご…　ごめん！
S-Sorry!
私の方こそ　ごめんなさい
I-I'm sorry, too.
梨穂子！
純一！
Rihoko!
Junichi!
梨穂子
Rihoko.
好きだ
えッ！？
I like you.
違う…
えッ？
No.
いつも近くにいたから
気づけなかったけど
I never noticed because we've always been close...
But I've been in love with you all this time, Rihoko.
僕　ずっと梨穂子が
好きだったんだ
ようやく
それが分かったよ
I know that well now, though.
私も純一のことが好き　だから
I love you too, Junichi.
That's why...
これからも　ずっと
一緒にいたいなって思ってる
I want to be with you from now on, forever.
このお茶　おいしいな
This tea's really good.
うん　玉露だからね
Yeah, it's high-quality green tea.
Enbi
Isn't it because you prepared the tea well?
梨穂子のいれ方が
いいんじゃないか？
そうかな？　好きな人のために
いれたからかな
Really?
Maybe it's because I was making it for the guy I like...
Morning!
おっはよ～う！
Huh?
あれ　２人とも顔が赤くない？
Your faces are pretty red.
M-Maybe it's because the tea's hot.
お…　お茶が熱いのかな？
部屋が暑いのかな？
Maybe it's because it's hot in here.
Something's weird.
何か　変なの～
へ…　変じゃないぞ
N-Nothing's weird!
何　ムキになってんの？
Why are you so mad?
I'm not mad!
ムキになんか　なってないぞ
You are.
≪（美也）なってるよ
なってないよ
I'm not.
怪しくない　ちょうどいい
Nothing's strange. It's all good.
朝を運ぶバイクの音が
Asa wo hakobu baiku no oto ga
The sound of bicycles each morning brings
ボクに時の流れ告げ
Boku ni toki no nagare tsuge
Tells me of the passage of time
もうどこへもいけない気持ち
Mou doko e mo ikenai kimochi
My feelings have nowhere else to go
キミに渡す覚悟決めた
Kimi ni watasu kakugo kimeta
I've decided to tell you about them
未来にちりばめた予定は隣に キミがいて欲しい
Mirai ni chiribameta yotei wa tonari ni kimi ga ite hoshii
I want you right by my side in my plans for the future
息を吸って吐き出す
Iki wo sutte hakidasu
I take deep breaths in and out
言葉は幾度も溜息に変わるけど
Kotoba wa ikudo mo tameiki ni kawaru kedo
My words keep turning into sighs
伝えたい言葉はただ一つだけ
Tsutaetai kotoba wa tada hitotsu dake
But there's just one thing I want you to know
「好きだよ」
Suki da yo
"I love you"
ボクの告白
Boku no kokuhaku
It's my confession
〈次回　予告〉
Preview
Next episode preview.
〈（響）ついに来週から
七咲ね　橘君〉
It's finally Nanasaki's turn next week, Tachibana-kun.
〈塚原先輩〉
〈私が卒業したあとも〉
Tsukahara-senpai.
〈うまくいってるようで
何よりだわ〉
I'm glad things have been going well since I graduated.
〈はい　おかげさまで〉
〈ただね〉
I n f i r m a r y
Yes, thanks to you.
〈ただ　何？〉
〈あの子　自分の気持ち〉
It's just...
Just what?
〈素直に口にできない
とこがあるから〉
There are times when she can't bring herself to say what's on her mind.
〈もしかしたら　本心を
隠してるかもって〉
She could be hiding her true feelings.
〈やめてくださいよ〉
Hey, gimme a break!
Next Episode
Nanasaki Ai
1st Half
Bold Front
Next Episode
Nanasaki Ai
1st Half
Bold Front
Next Episode
Nanasaki Ai
1st Half
Next episode: "Bold Front".
〈恋愛は人を
強くもさせるけど〉
Love can make someone strong,
but it can also make someone weak.
〈弱くも
させるものだから〉